Inventory of the National Cattlemen’s Association records, 1898-2018
University of Wyoming. American Heritage Center.
- Audio-Visual Materials, Series XVI.
  - Motion Pictures, Subseries 4.
    - Bre module (VHS), 1999-2003 (Box 701)
    - BSE/Oprah stuff etc. (VHS), undated (Box 701)
    - Burson - Marsteller, media training (VHS), November 15, 2001 (Box 701)
    - Bush speech (DVD), 2007 (Digital, Folder ahcdm_01713_018)
    - Cattle and Beef Production B-roll - NCBA and Beef Checkoff (Betacam), 2006 (Box 708)
    - CBB & NCBA, video of U.S. cattle and related scenes (Betacam), undated (Box 708)
    - Death Taxes - NBC Nightly News (VHS), August 24, 2000 (Box 701)
    - Federal News Service (FNS): CBS Evening News - Mad Cow disease (VHS), 2003 (Box 708)
    - Grazing and Wildlife (U-matic), undated (Box 701)
    - Grazing and Wildlife (U-matic), undated (Box 708)
    - HDV camera reactions to Bush speech (DVD), undated (Digital, Folder ahcdm_01713_021)
    - Home Food safety (VHS), undated (Box 708)
    - The Importance of Environmental Stewardship Award Program (VHS), 2003 (Box 701)
    - Izaak Walton League of America Presents Outdoor Ethics (2 VHS), 2001 (Box 708)
    - Master Cattle Transporter Training (DVD/CD), undated (Digital, Folder ahcdm_01713_014A-014B)
    - Max Baucus U.S. senator from Montana (DVD), October 29, 2010 (Digital, Folder ahcdm_01713_003)
    - Mike Schmidt - hay cutting (VHS), undated (Box 708)
    - NCBA 2003 Meeting OGS Opener (VHS) (Box 708)
    - NCBA Five Nation beef Conference, tapes 1-12 (3 VHS), 1999-2003 (Box 701)
    - NCBA live - RFD TV (VHS), 2004 (Box 708)
    - NCBA Policy Video News (2 VHS), 2000-2001 (Box 708)
    - NCBA Public Relations Tool Kit B-roll (Betacam), 2001 (Box 708)
    - NCBA Video News (2 VHS, U-matic), 1999-2000 (Box 708)
    - NCBA Video News (8 VHS), 1999-2001 (Box 701)
    - The Outdoor Magazine - "Beaverhead National Forest: A Multi-Use Success Story" (VHS), undated (Box 701)
    - The Outdoor Magazine Television Series - "Big Park" (VHS), undated (Box 708)
    - Owyhee River Rangeland (VHS), 1999 (Box 708)
    - PLC v. Babbitt KUSA Channel 9 (4 VHS), October 14, 1999 (Box 701)
    - President Bush Speech at the 2002 Cattle Industry Convention (VHS) (Box 701)
    - Ranches Collapse Under Death Tax: Personal Stories (VHS), 2000-2002 (Box 701)
    - Roots of Stewardship (VHS), undated (Box 708)
    - Taxation bill - Channel 9 News (VHS), November 14, 2000 (Box 701)
    - U.S. Beef Industry Response to Risk Assessment of BSE in the U.S. (2 Betacams), undated (Box 708)
    - We Need Water (VHS), 2001 (Box 708)
    - West Wing (VHS), 2001 (Box 708)
    - Western states cattle grazing B-roll - NCA (Betacam), 1993 (Box 708)
- Oversized Materials, Series XVII.
  - Scrapbooks, Subseries 1.
    - Scrapbooks, 1930-1942, 1973 (Box 678, Folders 1-3)
    - Ledgers, 1922-1927, 1943-1944 (Box 678, Folders 4-5)
  - Ledgers, Subseries 2.
    - Journals, 1950-1956 (Box 679, Folders 1-2)
    - Journal, 1957-1959 (Box 680, Folder 1)
    - Ledgers, 1942-1943, 1946, 1948-1949 (Box 680, Folders 2-4)
    - Ledgers, 1916-1934 (Box 681, Folders 1-2)
    - Membership Books, 1910-1916, 1920-1925 (Box 682, Folders 1-2)
    - Membership Book, 1924-1927 (Box 683, Folder 1)
    - Annual Dues Journal, 1927-1936 (Box 683, Folder 2)
    - Ledgers, 1934-1942 (Box 684, Folders 1-2)
    - Ledgers, 1944-1948 (Box 685, Folders 1-2)
  - Artifacts, Subseries 3.
    - Phillips County Cattlewomen brand blanket, 1956-1999 (Box 710)
    - United States Flag, undated (Box 710)
    - Welcome Public Lands Council banner, undated (Box 710)